Guide to the Pittsburgh Public School Records AIS.1966.18a
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Pittsburgh Public School Records
1855-ca. 1995
ULS Archives & Special Collections
AIS.1966.18a
5 boxes
- Allegheny City Schools
  - Allegheny City Board of Controllers
    - Minute Book, March 1878- March 1886
    - Minute Book, 1886-1891
    - Minute Book, 1891-1896
    - Minute Book, 1896-1900
    - Minute Book, 1900-1904
    - Minute Book, 1904-1906
    - Minute Book, 1909-1911
    - Committe on Committees Minute Book, 1900-1911
    - Finance Committee Minute Book, 1887-1911
    - High School Committee Minute Book, 1895-1902
    - High School Committee Minute Book, 1902-1911
    - School Supplies Committee Minute Book, 1889-1911
  - 1st Ward
    - Board Minute Book, 1878-1888
    - Board Minute Book, 1888-1908
    - Board Minute Book, 1908-1911
    - Board Minute Book, 1908-1911
    - Board Auditing Committee Minute Book, 1876-1894
    - Treasurer's Fiscal Account Book, 1876-1912
    - Treasurer's Disbursement Ledger, 1909-1911
  - 2nd Ward
    - Board Minute Book, 1909-1911
  - 3rd Ward
    - Board Minute Book, 1900-1911
  - 4th Ward
    - Board Minute Book, 1840-1848
    - Board Minute Book, 1849-1854
    - Board Minute Book, 1896-1911
    - Board Ledger, 1846-1880
    - Board Ledger, 1880-1911
  - 5th Ward
    - Board Minute Book, 1906-1911
  - 6th Ward
    - Board Minute Book, 1903-1911
  - 7th Ward
    - Board Minute Book, 1854-1865
    - Board Minute Book, 1877-1907
    - Board Minute Book, 1907-1911
    - Treasurer's Ledger Book, 1877-1899
    - Treasurer's Ledger Book, 1910-1911
    - Report of Audit of Accounts and Records of the Former 7th Ward, August 1912
  - 8th Ward
    - Board Minute Book, 1901-1911
    - Cash Book, 1886-1911
    - Treasurer's Receipts, 1898-1911
  - 9th Ward
    - Board Minute Book, 1897-1911
  - 10th Ward
    - Board Minute Book, 1903-1911
  - 11th Ward
    - Board Minute Book, 1859-1898
    - Board Minute Book, 1898-1911
  - 12th Ward
    - Board Minute Book, 1896-1909
    - Board Minute Book, 1909-1911
    - Board Ledger Book, 1887-1911
  - 13th Ward
    - Board Minute Book, 1903-1911
  - 15th Ward
    - Board Minute Book, 1906-1911
  - Beechview Borough
    - Board Minute Book, 1905-1911
  - Carrick Borough, 1905-1906
    - Financial and Maintenance Documents, 1905-1906 (Folder 1)
    - Board Minute Book, 1904-1917
    - Board Minute Book, 1917-1925
    - Board Minute Book, 1925-1926
    - Monthly Time Book, 1920-1926
  - Chartiers Township, 1897-1917
    - Maintenance Documents, 1897-1917 (Folder 1)
    - Board Minute Book, 1893-1896
    - Board Minute Book, 1896-1898
    - Board Minute Book, 1898-1904
    - Board Minute Book, 1909-1911
    - Board Minute Book, 1917-1921
    - Tax Receipt Book, 1918
    - Tax Receipt Book, 1919
    - Tax Valuation, A-M, 1918
    - Tax Valuation, N-Z, 1918
  - Lawrenceville
    - Board Minute Book, 1840-1850
    - Board Minute Book, 1858-1865
  - Knoxville
    - Board Minute Book, 1858-1865
    - Union High School Board Minute Book, 1921-1927
    - Union High School Treasurer Cash Book, 1921-1927
  - Union Township, 1916-1927
    - Board Minute Book, 1920-1927
    - Account Book, 1927
    - Ledger of School Exonerations, 1916-1922 (Folder 1)
    - Receipts from Eugene Euscoe, 1925-1927 (Folder 2)
    - School Director Certifications (Folder 3)
- Annual Reports of the Board of Education
  - 1st Annual Report, 1912 (Volume 1)
  - 2nd Annual Report, 1913 (Volume 2)
  - 3rd Annual Report, 1914 (Volume 3)
  - 4th Annual Report, 1915 (Volume 4)
  - 5th Annual Report, 1916 (Volume 5)
  - 6th Annual Report, 1917 (Volume 6)
  - 7th Annual Report, 1918 (Volume 7)
  - 8th Annual Report, 1919 (Volume 8)
  - 9th Annual Report, 1920 (Volume 9)
  - 10th Annual Report, 1921 (Volume 10)
  - 11th Annual Report, 1922 (Volume 11)
  - 12th Annual Report, 1923 (Volume 12)
  - 13th Annual Report, 1924 (Volume 13)
  - 14th Annual Report, 1925 (Volume 14)
  - 15th Annual Report, 1926 (Volume 15)
  - 16th Annual Report, 1927 (Volume 16)
  - 17th Annual Report, 1928 (Volume 17)
  - 18th Annual Report, 1929 (Volume 18)
  - 19th Annual Report, 1930 (Volume 19)
  - 20th Annual Report, 1931 (Volume 20)
  - 21th Annual Report, 1932 (Volume 21)
  - 22nd Annual Report, 1933 (Volume 22)
  - 23rd Annual Report, 1934 (Volume 23)
  - 24th Annual Report, 1935 (Volume 24)
  - 25th Annual Report, 1936 (Volume 25)
  - 26th Annual Report, 1937 (Volume 26)
  - 27th Annual Report, 1938 (Volume 27)
  - 28th Annual Report, 1939 (Volume 28)
  - 29th Annual Report, 1940 (Volume 29)
  - 30th Annual Report, 1941 (Volume 30)
  - 31st Annual Report, 1942 (Volume 31)
  - 32nd Annual Report, 1943 (Volume 32)
  - 33rd Annual Report, 1944 (Volume 33)
  - 34th Annual Report, 1945 (Volume 34)
- Annual Reports of the Secretary and Business Manager for the Board of Public Education, 1950-1961
  - Thirty Ninth Annual Report, 1950
  - Fortieth Annual Report, 1951
  - Forty First Annual Report, 1952
  - Forty Second Annual Report, 1953
  - Forty Third Annual Report, 1954
  - Forty Fourth Annual Report, 1955
  - Forty Fifth Annual Report, 1956
  - Forty Sixth Annual Report, 1957
  - Forty Seventh Annual Report, 1958
  - Forty Ninth Annual Report, 1960
  - Forty Eighth Annual Report, 1959
  - Fiftieth Annual Report, 1961
- Annual Reports of the Superintendent, 1930-1962
  - 1930 (Folder 1)
  - 1931-1932 (Folder 2)
  - 1932-1933 (Folder 3)
  - 1933-1934 (Folder 4)
  - 1934-1935 (Folder 5)
  - 1935-1936 (Folder 6)
  - 1936-1937 (Folder 7)
  - 1937-1938 (Folder 8)
  - 1938-1939 (Folder 9)
  - 1939-1940 (Folder 10)
  - 1940-1941 (Folder 11)
  - 1941-1942 (Folder 12)
  - 1942-1943 (Folder 13)
  - 1943-1944 (Folder 14)
  - 1944-1945 (Folder 15)
  - 1945-1946 (Folder 16)
  - 1946-1947 (Folder 17)
  - 1947-1948 (Folder 18)
  - 1948-1949 (Folder 19)
  - 1949-1950 (Folder 20)
  - 1950-1951 (Folder 21)
  - 1951-1952 (Folder 22)
  - 1952-1953 (Folder 23)
  - 1953-1954 (Folder 24)
  - 1954-1955 (Folder 25)
  - 1955-1956 (Folder 26)
  - 1956-1957 (Folder 27)
  - 1957-1958 (Folder 28)
  - 1958-1959 (Folder 29)
  - 1959-1960 (Folder 30)
  - 1960-1961 (Folder 31)
  - 1961-1962 (Folder 32)
- Board of Education, Minute books, 1911-1945, 1953-1997
- Central Board of Education, Minute books
  - Minute book A, 1855-1865 (Volume A)
  - Minute book B, 1865-1871 (Volume B)
  - Minute book C, 1872-1877 (Volume C)
  - Minute book D, 1877-1882 (Volume D)
  - Minute book E, 1882-1890 (Volume E)
- Pittsburgh Central High School, 1855-1906
  - Principal's Reports, 1870-1878
  - Principal's Reports, 1878-1886
  - Vacation School Record Book, 1901
  - Alphabetic Index, 1892-1901
  - Alphabetic Index, 1898-1902
  - Academic Department
    - Grade Book, Class A, 1889-1890
    - Grade Book, Class A, 1890-1891
    - Grade Book, Class A, 1893-1894
    - Grade Book, Class B, 1889-1890
    - Grade Book, Class B, 1890-1891
    - Grade Book, Class B, 1892-1893
    - Grade Book, Class C, 1889-1890
    - Grade Book, Class C, 1889-1890
    - Grade Book, Class C, 1890-1891
    - Grade Book, Class C, 1890-1891
    - Grade Book, Class C, 1890-1891
    - Grade Book, Class C, 1890-1891
    - Grade Book, Class C, 1892-1893
    - Grade Book, Class C, 1892-1893
    - Grade Book, Class C, 1892-1893
    - Grade Book, Class D, 1888-1889
    - Grade Book, Class D, 1888-1889
    - Grade Book, Class D, 1888-1889
    - Grade Book, Class D, 1889-1890
    - Grade Book, Class D, 1889-1890
    - Grade Book, Class D, 1889-1890
    - Grade Book, Class D, 1890-1891
    - Grade Book, Class D, 1890-1891
    - Grade Book, Class D, 1890-1891
    - Grade Book, Class D, 1892-1893
    - Grade Book, Class D, 1892-1893
    - Grade Book, Class D, 1892-1893
    - Grade Book, Class D, 1892-1893
    - Grade Book, Class D (Normal), 1889-1890
    - Grade Book, Class D (Normal), 1890-1891
    - Grade Book, Class D (Normal), 1891-1892
    - Grade Book, Class D (Normal), 1892-1893
    - Grade Book, Class D (Normal), 1893-1894
    - Grade Book, Class D (Normal), 1895-1896
    - Grade Book, Class N (Normal), 1892-1893
    - Enrollment Records, 1855-1856
    - Enrollment Records, 1855-1876
    - Enrollment Records, 1859-1870
    - Enrollment Records, 1875-1891
    - Enrollment Records, 1876-1895
    - Enrollment Records, 1883-1888
    - Enrollment Records, 1888-1892
    - Enrollment Records, 1892-1898
    - Enrollment Records, 1898-1906
  - Commercial Department
    - Grade Book, 1884-1885
    - Grade Book, 1885-1886
    - Grade Book, 1886-1887
    - Grade Book, 1887-1888
    - Grade Book, 1888-1889
    - Grade Book, 1889-1890
    - Grade Book, 1890-1891
    - Enrollment Records, 1876-1882
    - Enrollement Records, 1890-1897
    - Enrollement Records, 1898-1903
- Dr. William D. McCoy's Research, 1948-1959
  - "History of Pittsburgh Public Schools"
    - Chapter 1: Organization and First Years of School
    - Chapter 2: Development and Expansion 1837-1855
    - Chapter 3: Reorganization Under County 1855-1868
    - Chapter 4: Operation Under First City Superintendent 1868-1898
    - Chapter 5: Operation and Development 1898 to 1911: Annexation of Allegheny
    - Chapter 6: Consolidation and Reorganization 1911-1920
    - Chapter 7: Expansion and Development of High and Trade Schools 1920-1935
    - Miscellaneous: Volume 1
    - Miscellaneous: Volume 2
    - Miscellaneous: Volume 3
  - McCoy Research
    - Bibliography & Sources, ca. 1958
    - Ben Graham: Related Materials, 1941-1942
    - Index Files: Baxter-West Library
    - Index & Reseacrch Files
    - Maps Drawn by McCoy, 1959 & an 1869 Pittsburgh Map
    - Newspaper Clips
    - Greater Pittsburgh, February 1949
    - McCoy Photographs and Photostats
    - Pittsburgh Education Histories, 1904-1958
    - Newsletters and Bulletins, 1936-1961
    - Special Services Offered in the Elementary Schools, by Marie Saul, January 1955
    - Education System During World War 2
    - Pittsburgh Growth and Population Information, 1934
    - Brief Description of the New Administration Building of the Board of Public Education
    - Charette Magazine, March 1962
    - Fifty Years in Pittsburgh Schools, George W. Gerwig, September-December 1942
    - Handbook: Information Pittsburgh Public High Schools, June 1916
    - The Nature of Early Education, Tri-State Area School Study Council
    - Pittsburgh Public Schools: Buildings, Supplies, Personnel, Enrollment, Administration, Board of Public Education, 1935
    - Pittsburgh Schools: Growth of Public Education in Pittsburgh, September-December 1958
    - The Pittsburgh School System
    - The Pittsburgh School System: Voter's League Report, 1911
    - Pittsburgh High School, 1904-1905
    - A Short History of the Public High Schools of Pittsburgh (2)
    - Student Life in Schools of the Ohio Valley Ninety Years Ago, by Stanton C. Crawford & John A. Nietz, December 1940
    - The Truth About the Schools (Reoirt from The Pittsburgh Sun), May 1922
    - Bedford Annual Picnic Pin, 1909
    - Central High School: 100 Year History, 1959
    - Colfax School Programs, 1905-1906
    - Duquesne School Reunion Medal
    - Fifth Avenue News: 50 Years of Fifth Ave High, 1946
    - First 4 Schools: (North, South, East, West) History
    - First Ward School Reunion, 1905
    - Hazelwood: 1872-1937, May 1937
    - Hiland Schools History
    - History of Liberty Schools, May 1893
    - Lincoln Schools History
    - Mt. Albion History
    - Troy Hill History
    - Schenley Reunion, June 1920
- Courses of Study, 1917-1970
  - Aeronautics, October 1929, February 1942, April 1942, September 1943, November 1943
  - Art Education, Chart for Evaluating the Development of the Child through Art Activities: Primary-Senior High Schools, 1931
  - Auditorium Practice, Grades 1B-6A, 1939
  - Safe Automobile Driving, 1938
  - Biology, Study Guide for Biology, 1936, 1960
  - Junior Business Grade 9, 1930, 1934
  - Bookkeeping I, September 1928
  - Bookkeeping II, September 1929
  - Commercial Arithmetic, 1918, September 1935
  - Typewriting, September 1952
  - Chemistry, 1931
  - Chemistry: Manual of Directions for Tests, 1937
  - Civics Junior Division, September 1935, 1936
  - Civics Grade 12B, 1933
  - Economics High School, June 1940
  - English Grades 1-6, 1926-1928
  - English (Written) Grades 1-6, May 1950
  - English Junior High School, 1922-1923
  - English Grades 7-9, 1927
  - English Grades 7-9, 1939-1941
  - English Grades 7-12, 1952-1955
  - English Composition, Grades 10-12, 1939-1941
  - English Composition Grades 7-12, 1966-1967
  - English Instruction Materials Grades 7-12
  - Grade Allocation of Word Study in Junior and Senior High Schools, 1943
  - Suggested Material for Correlated Work in English, Undated
  - First Aid, Grades 4-6 and 7-12, 1942
  - Geography Grades 3-8, 1921-1922
  - Geography Grades 4-6, 1936
  - Handwriting Grades 1-8, 1922, 1937
  - History Elementary, 1921, 1933, 1937
  - History Junior High School, 1937
  - Home Economics Grades 1-11, 1945
  - Chemistry Laboratory Manuals, High School, 1933
  - Home Economics Grade 8, 1939
  - Home Economics Grade 9, 1939
  - Home Economics I and II, 1941
  - Home Economics III and IV, 1942
  - Home Economics V-VIII, 1942
  - Home Economics Elementary and Junior High, 1950-1951
  - Home Economics, Household Art and Millinery, Senior Class, 1918
  - Secondary Home Economics: Social Living, Grades 11-12, 1951
  - Guidance, Elementary School, 1940
  - Guidance, Junior High SChool, 1939-1940
  - Guidance, High School, 1922
  - Language Arts, Grades 4-6, 1955
  - Language Arts, Intercultural Education, Grades 1-12, 1944
  - Library Practice, Grades 2-6, 1935
  - Mathematics, Grades 1-6, February 1950, September 1955
  - Mathematics, Junior High School, November 1945, April 1957, April 1958
  - Music, Elementary School, 1921, 1934, 1960
  - Music, Junior and Senior Divisions, 1927, 1937
  - Physical Education and Health, Grades K-3, 1942
  - Physical Education, Grades 1-2, undated
  - Physical Education and Health, Grades 1-8, 1947-1949
  - Physical Education and Health, Handbook on Girls Athletics in the Junior and Senior High Schools, 1929
  - Physical Education and Health, Junior and Senior HIgh School Girls, 1943
  - Physical Education and Health, Grades 4-6, 1942
  - Pysical and Health Education, Junior and Senior High Schools, 1942-1943
  - Physical Education and Health, Grades 10-12, 1936
  - Languages, Junior and Senior High Schools, 1918, 1927, undated
  - Physical Education Health Chart, 1941
  - Physical Education and Health, Music for Games, Rhythmic Work, Folk Dances, Grades 1-8, Undated
  - Physical Education and Health, Physical Efficiency Test, Junior and Senior High Schools, 1922
  - Physical Education and Health, Regulations for High School Boys' Track and Field Athletic Activities, 1935
  - Physics, High School, 1917-1918
  - Outline and Content for Physics Text "Physics for the New Age", 1947
  - Programs of Study, Junior and Senior High School, 1930-1933
  - Science, Elemtary School, 1917, 1921, 1928, 1941
  - Science, Grades 7-8, 1941, 1945
  - Science, Grade 9, 1941
  - Science, Grades 1 and 4, 1970
  - Science, Grades 5 and 8, 1964, 1970
  - Science, High School, 1927
  - Science, Physical Science, Senior High School, 1959, 1961
  - Science, Teachers Study Guide, Grade 9, undated
  - Sociology, Grade 12, 1940
  - Social Studies, Grade 8, 1945, 1955
  - Social Studies, Grade 9, 1939-1940
  - Social Studies, Grade 11, 1943-1944
  - Social Studies, Languages, Grade 7, 1938
  - Social Studies, World History, Grade 10, 1935
  - Social Studies, World History, 1942
  - Special Classes, 1931
  - Subject and Time Distribution, 1930-1933
  - Suggestions for Teachers of SLow-Learning Pupils in Junior High Schools, 1946
  - Thrift, Elementary, 1921
  - Veterans Training Program, undated
  - Victory Garden, Grade 6, 1943
  - Junior Prevocational Classes, 1936
  - Vocational, Automobile, 1926
  - Vocational: Beauty Culture Theory, 1936
  - Vocational, Electricity, undated
  - Vocational, Electric Power Equipment, 1926
  - Vocational, Electorical Wiring, 1926
  - Vocational, Printing, 1926, 1931
  - Vocational, Woodwork, Grades 9-12, 1937
  - Zoology, 1929
- Allen Sub-District
  - Board Minute Book, 1901-1910
  - Board Minute Book, 1910-1911
- Bedford Sub-District, 1900-1911
  - Financial Documents, 1900-1911 (Folder 1)
  - Board Minute Book, 1894-1904
  - Board Minute Book, 1904-1911
- Beltzhoover Sub-District, 1904-1913
  - Maintenance Documents, 1904-1913 (Folder 1)
  - Board Minute Book, 1899-1909
  - Board Minute Book, 1909-1911
  - Treasurer's Record Book, 1899-1909
- Birmingham Sub-District
  - Board Minute Book, 1898-1912
- Brushton Sub-District, 1906-1911
  - Board Minute Book, 1906-1911
- Colfax Sub-District, 1906-1911
  - Board Minute Book, 1906-1911
  - Letter from Union National Bank, undated (Folder 1)
- Crescent Sub-District, 1906-1911
  - Board Minute Book, 1906-1909
  - Board Minute Book, 1909-1911
  - Financial Ledger, 1906-1911
- Duquesne Sub-District, 1904-1911
  - Board Minute Book, 1904-1909
  - Board Minute Book, 1909-1911
  - Board Minute Book (Preliminary), 1909-1911
- Esplen Sub-District, 1901-1911
  - Board Minute Book, June 1901-November 1911
  - Receipts, September 1911 (Folder 1)
- Forbes Sub-District (Forbes and Second Avenue), 1907-1911
  - Board Minute Book, March 1907- November 1911
  - Expense Report, June 1908 (Folder 1)
  - Cover of Loan Bond from Washington Trust Company, 1911 (Folder 2)
- Franklin Sub-District, 1881-1911
  - Board Minute Book, July 1901- November 1911
  - Board Minute Book, June 1911
- Grant Sub-District, 1902-1927
  - Board Minute Book, 1902-1911
  - Immigrant School Enrollment Books, 1926-1927
  - Immigrant School Enrollment Books, 1924-1926
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Catherine Holland, 1st Semester, 1912 (Folder 1)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Catherine Holland, 1st Semester (1), 1913-1914 (Folder 2)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Catherine Holland, 1st Semester (2), 1913-1914 (Folder 3)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Catherine Holland, 1st Semester (1), 1915 (Folder 4)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Catherine Holland, 1st Semester (2), 1915 (Folder 5)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Catherine Holland, 1st Semester (1), 1916 (Folder 6)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Catherine Holland, 1st Semester (2), 1916 (Folder 7)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Catherine Holland, 1st Semester (3), 1916 (Folder 8)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Catherine Holland, 2nd Semester (1), 1916 (Folder 9)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Catherine Holland, 2nd Semester (2), 1916 (Folder 10)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Catherine Holland, 1917 (Folder 11)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Catherine Holland, 1st Semester, 1917 (Folder 12)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Catherine Holland, 2nd Semester, 1917 (Folder 13)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Catherine Holland, 1918 (Folder 14)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Catherine Holland, 2nd Semester, 1918 (Folder 15)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Catherine Holland, 2nd Semester, 1919 (Folder 16)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Alice Leech, 2nd Semester, 1913 (Folder 17)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Sarah G. Lowry, February 1927-June 1927 (Folder 18)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Mariam Neiman, 2nd Semester, 1917 (Folder 19)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Mary Nolin, 2nd Semester, 1914 (Folder 20)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Mary Nolin, 1st Semester, 1915 (Folder 21)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Mary Nolin, 1st Semester, 1916 (Folder 22)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Mary Nolin, 2nd Semester, 1916 (Folder 23)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Mary Nolin, 1st Semester, 1917 (Folder 24)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Mary Nolin, 2nd Semester, 1917 (Folder 25)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Mary Nolin, 2nd Semester, 1918 (Folder 26)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Mary Nolin, 2nd Semester, 1920 (Folder 27)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Mary Nolin, 1st Semester (1), 1920-1921 (Folder 28)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Mary Nolin, 1st Semester (2), 1920-1921 (Folder 29)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Mary Nolin, 2nd Semester (1), 1920-1921 (Folder 30)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Mary Nolin, 2nd Semester (2), 1920-1921 (Folder 31)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Mary Nolin, 2nd Semester (3), 1920-1921 (Folder 32)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Mary Nolin, 1st Semester (1), 1921 (Folder 33)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Mary Nolin, 1st Semester (2), 1921 (Folder 34)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Mary Nolin, 1st Semester (1), 1921-1922 (Folder 35)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Mary Nolin, 1st Semester (2), 1921-1922 (Folder 36)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Mary Nolin, 2nd Semester (1), 1921-1922 (Folder 37)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Mary Nolin, 2nd Semester (2), 1921-1922 (Folder 38)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Mary Nolin, 2nd Semester (1), 1922 (Folder 39)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Mary Nolin, 2nd Semester (2), 1922 (Folder 40)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Mary Nolin, 1st Semester (1), 1922-1923 (Folder 41)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Mary Nolin, 1st Semester (2), 1922-1923 (Folder 42)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, 1917-1921 (Folder 43)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, 1st Semester, 1922-1923 (Folder 44)
- Greentree Borough, 1913
  - Financial Report, 1913 (Folder 1)
- Hancock Sub-District, 1871-1939
  - Board Minute Books, May 1871- October 1896
  - Board Minute Books, November 1896- November 1911
  - School Docket: Immigrant Classes, 1930-1939
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Mrs. Carson, September 1927 (Folder 1)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Mrs. Carson, February 1927- June 1927 (Folder 2)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Mrs. Carson, June 1927-June 1928 (Folder 3)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Mrs. Carson, 1927-1930 (Folder 4)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Mrs. Carson, 1929 (Folder 5)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Mrs. Carson, 1930 (Folder 6)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Mrs. Carson, undated (Folder 7)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Jean Cuy, September 1931- June 1932 (Folder 8)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Anna Emory Johnson, February 1926-June 1926 (Folder 9)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Anna Emory Johnson, September 1927- February 1929 (Folder 10)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Anna Emory Johnson, February 1929- June 1929 (Folder 11)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Anna Emory Johnson, September 1929- June 1930 (Folder 12)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Blanche Pollock, 1927-1928 (Folder 13)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Blanche Pollock, 1928-1929 (Folder 14)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Blanche Pollock, 1929-1930 (Folder 15)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Blanche Pollock, 1930-1931 (Folder 16)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Blanche Pollock, 1931-1932 (Folder 17)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Blanche Pollock, September 1932- June 1933 (Folder 18)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Blanche Pollock, 1933-1934 (Folder 19)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Blanche Pollock, 1934-1935 (Folder 20)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Blanche Pollock, 1935-1937 (Folder 21)